{
  "Quiz": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "roomId": 1,
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What’s the biggest planet in our solar system?",
          "options": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Mercury"],
          "correct_option": "Jupiter"
        },
        {
          "question": "What attraction in India is one of the famus in the world?",
          "options": ["Chand Minar", "Taj Mahal", "Stadium"],
          "correct_option": "Taj Mahal"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "roomId": 2,
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What’s the biggest planet in our solar system?",
          "options": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Mercury"],
          "correct_option": "Jupiter"
        },
        {
          "question": "10 FISHES ARE IN THE TANK , 2 DROWN 4 SWIM AWAY AND 3 DIED HOW MANY ARE LEFT ?",
          "options": ["10", "3", "0"],
          "correct_option": "3"
        },
        {
          "question": "A grandfather, two fathers and two sons went to the movie theater together and everyone bought one movie ticket each. How many tickets did they buy in total?",
          "options": ["3", "2", "5", "1"],
          "correct_option": "2"
        },
        {
          "question": "WHAT ENGLISH WORD HAS THREE CONSECUTIVE DOUBLE LETTERS ?",
          "options": ["shopkeeper", "door", "bookkeeper", "three"],
          "correct_option": "three"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the only flying mammal?",
          "options": [
            "The bat",
            "The flying squirrel",
            "The bald eagle",
            "The colugo"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The bat"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "roomId": 3,
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What’s the biggest planet in our solar system?",
          "options": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Mercury"],
          "correct_option": "Jupiter"
        },
        {
          "question": "What attraction in India is one of the famus in the world?",
          "options": ["Chand Minar", "Taj Mahal", "Stadium"],
          "correct_option": "Taj Mahal"
        },
        {
          "question": "What land animal can open its mouth the widest?",
          "options": ["Alligator", "Crocodile", "Baboon", "Hippo"],
          "correct_option": "Hippo"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the largest animal on Earth?",
          "options": [
            "The African elephant",
            "The blue whale",
            "The sperm whale",
            "The giant squid"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The blue whale"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the only flying mammal?",
          "options": [
            "The bat",
            "The flying squirrel",
            "The bald eagle",
            "The colugo"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The bat"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "roomId": 4,
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What’s the biggest planet in our solar system?",
          "options": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Mercury"],
          "correct_option": "Jupiter"
        },
        {
          "question": "What attraction in India is one of the famus in the world?",
          "options": ["Chand Minar", "Taj Mahal", "Stadium"],
          "correct_option": "Taj Mahal"
        },
        {
          "question": "What land animal can open its mouth the widest?",
          "options": ["Alligator", "Crocodile", "Baboon", "Hippo"],
          "correct_option": "Hippo"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the largest animal on Earth?",
          "options": [
            "The African elephant",
            "The blue whale",
            "The sperm whale",
            "The giant squid"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The blue whale"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the only flying mammal?",
          "options": [
            "The bat",
            "The flying squirrel",
            "The bald eagle",
            "The colugo"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The bat"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "roomId": 5,
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What’s the biggest planet in our solar system?",
          "options": ["Jupiter", "Saturn", "Neptune", "Mercury"],
          "correct_option": "Jupiter"
        },
        {
          "question": "What attraction in India is one of the famus in the world?",
          "options": ["Chand Minar", "Taj Mahal", "Stadium"],
          "correct_option": "Taj Mahal"
        },
        {
          "question": "What land animal can open its mouth the widest?",
          "options": ["Alligator", "Crocodile", "Baboon", "Hippo"],
          "correct_option": "Hippo"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the largest animal on Earth?",
          "options": [
            "The African elephant",
            "The blue whale",
            "The sperm whale",
            "The giant squid"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The blue whale"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the only flying mammal?",
          "options": [
            "The bat",
            "The flying squirrel",
            "The bald eagle",
            "The colugo"
          ],
          "correct_option": "The bat"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
